

CONTACT

iafhurtado@gmail.com

(174) 239 70774

github.com/iafhurtado

🏠 Hamburg, Germany

EDUCATION

KÜHNE LOGISTICS UNIVERSITY

2016

Master of Science in Global Logistics Hamburg, Germany

CERTIFICATES

META - FRONTEND DEVELOPER PROFESSIONAL

2023

Coursera

COMPUTER SKILLS

Atlassian suite
Azure DevOps
Figma
Github - Version Control
HTML & CSS
Notion
React.js

SOCIAL

linkedin: Ivan Flores Hurtado opensea.io/jaibo twitter.com/iafhurtado

IVAN FLORES HURTADO

Product Management and UX Design

ABOUT

Experienced leader with experience building products that customers love to use. My strength is to recognize the valid and actionable feedback from plain noise, the key is to bring all stakeholders together and efficiently move an idea from discovery to post-launch support.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

Aligning Stakeholders
Agile Development Facilitator
Backlog Grooming
Being the Voice-of-the-Customer
Third-Party Integrations
User Story/Epic Writing

Product Management Strategic Thinking Strategning Stakeholders Team Leadership Roadmapping & Execution UX Design & Research

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT LEADERSHIP & DESIGN

Selbständig - Freelancer | Sep 2020 - Present

- Help clients build their ideas working with strong product team members
- Think through Jobs-To-Be-Done and how to bring practical solutions to market
- Draft user-interaction diagram and front-end interfaces (Figma)
- Define contracts, modifiers, and functions for the smart contract (Remix)
- Gather feedback from users to improve on the next iteration
- Documentation and recording of most important information for the community

PRODUCT TEAM LEAD

FujiDAO Labs OÜ | Feb 2022 - Nov 2022

- Advocate as the voice-of-the-customer inside the development team
- Facilitating agile practices such as Brainstorming and Retrospective sessions
- Holding weekly feedback calls with stakeholders to solicit insights from front-lines
- Orchestrating work among different teams (Web vs iOS vs Android vs Agent)
- Executing the product strategy and holding everyone accountable



CONTACT

iafhurtado@gmail.com

(174) 239 70774

github.com/iafhurtado

Hamburg, Germany

EDUCATION (CONT.)

UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA

2010-2012

Bachelor of Science in Operations Management Tucson, Arizona

PIMA COMMUNITY COLLEGE

2008-2010

Business Administration Major

Tucson, Arizona

UDEMY CERTIFICATES

The complete Javascript Course

Jonas Schmedtmann

Learn Python Programming Masterclass

Tim Buchalka

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT MANAGER

Kühne + Nagel | Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

- Align stakeholders around a common roadmap (Customers, Dev Teams, Operations and Sales)
- Ensure continuous deployment across all Spring microservices
- Engineer requirements from customer feedback
- Brainstorm and mock-up interfaces to give designers and engineers as product perspective
- Evangelized Agile development and staying nimble inside the Dev team

PRODUCT OWNER

ShareHouse GmbH & Co. KG | May 2018 - Mar 2019

- Startup's first full-time employee
- Coordinated with an agency house to make sure product requirements were aligned
- Groom the backlog and estimate effort for tasks and user stories
- Helped interview new colleagues to grow the team up to 18 teammates
- Tested new releases for quality assurance and frictionless deployment

CO-FOUNDER & CEO

Clinch Logistics GmbH | Apr 2017 - Feb 2019

- Secured seed funding to build our MVP from Angel Investors in Hamburg
- · Hired core team of engineers
- Build in public at the Digital Hub Logistics in the Hafencity and participated in an accelerator from NUMA in Mexico City
- Conducted business development calls with early customers
- Gathered feedback from early users and integrated back into our backlog